Jane Fonda papers SSC.MS.00477
Sophia Smith Collection
- Writings, 1954-2014; 4; 12.93 linear feet (31 boxes)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Vadim, 2003-2005; 2 folders (Box 47, Folder 1-2)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, I'm Not Bourgoise [sic], 2003-2005; 1 folders (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, The Magician's Assistant, 2003-2005; 1 folders (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Putting Down Roots, 2003-2005; 1 folders (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Barbarella, 2003-2005; 1 folders (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, 1968, 2004; 1 folders (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, They Shoot Horses Don't They, 2003-2005; 1 folders (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Coming Home, 2003-2005; 3 folders (Box 47, Folder 9-11)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, This Is America, 2004; 1 folders (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Government Issue, 2003-2005; 1 folders (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, An Aside, 2003-2005; 3 folders (Box 47, Folder 14-16)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Snapshots from the Road, 2003-2005; 3 folders (Box 48, Folder 1-3)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Klute, 2003-2005; 1 folders (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, The New Warriors, 2003-2004; 3 folders (Box 48, Folder 5-7)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Redemption, 2003; 2 folders (Box 48, Folder 8-9)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Owning Leadership, 2004; 1 folders (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Insurrection and Sexuality, 2003; 1 folders (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Betwixt and Between, 2003; 1 folders (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Tom, 2003; 2 folders (Box 48, Folder 13-14)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Hanoi, 2003-2005; 3 folders (Box 49, Folder 1-3)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Bamboo, 2004; 1 folders (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Return to the Free World, 2004; 1 folders (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Framed, 2004; 2 folders (Box 49, Folder 6-7)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Adieu, Lone Ranger, 2003; 1 folders (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Peace at Hand?, 2003-2004; 1 folders (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Committed, 2003-2005; 2 folders (Box 49, Folder 10-11)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, The Final Push, 2003-2004; 4 folders (Box 49, Folder 12-15)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, David & Goliath, 2003-2005; 1 folders (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, I'm Baaack, 2003-2005; 3 folders (Box 49, Folder 17-19)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Beyond Protest, 2003; 1 folders (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Workout, 2004; 1 folders (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Laurel Springs, 2003-2005; 1 folders (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Ghost, 2003-2004; 1 folders (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Travels with Dolly, 2003-2005; 1 folders (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, On Golden Pond, 2003-2005; 5 folders (Box 50, Folder 6-10)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Closure, 2003-2005; 1 folders (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Movie Acting, 2003; 1 folders (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Winning, 2003-2005; 1 folders (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Creativity vs. Willpower, 2003-2004; 1 folders (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, The Gift of Pain, 2003-2004; 2 folders (Box 50, Folder 15-16)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Phoenix on Hold, 2003-2005; 1 folders (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Meanwhile, Back at the Ranch, 2003-2005; 1 folders (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Bewitched…, 2004; 1 folders (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Paradises, 2004; 2 folders (Box 51, Folder 1-2)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, A Calling, 2004; 1 folders (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Tom Hayden, 2003-2005; 3 folders (Box 51, Folder 4-6)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Act One: Chapter One: Butterflies, 2003-2005; 8 folders (Box 51, Folder 7-14)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Act One: Ch Two: Gene Pool, 2003-2005; 7 folders (Box 52, Folder 1-7)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Act One: Ch Two: Gene Pool, House Beautiful, July 1948; 1 folders (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Ripen the Time, 2004; 1 folders (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Klute, 2003-2005; 1 folders (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Leaving My Father's House, 2004; 2 folders (Box 52, Folder 10-11)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Moving On, 2004; 1 folders (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Sixty, 2004; 1 folders (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Act Three Beginning, 2003-2005; 1 folders (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Drafts, Yearnings, 2004; 4 folders (Box 52, Folder 15-18)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), General, Advertising Poster, 2000-2005; 1 folders (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), General, Authorized Book Extracts, 1 folders (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), General, Book Cover Design, 2000-2005; 1 folders (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), General, Book Press, 2001-2005; 4 folders (Box 53, Folder 2-5)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), General, Book Research, 1935-2001; 2 folders (Box 53, Folder 6-7)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), General, Book Rights, 2001-2006; 2 folders (Box 53, Folder 8-9)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), General, Book Tour Schedule, 2006; 1 folders (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), General, Court Cases, 1982-2004; 3 folders (Box 53, Folder 11-13)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), General, House Beautiful, Vol. 80, No. 7, 1 folders (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), General, People Who Got Signed Books, 1 folders (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), General, Publicity, 1 folders (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), General, Response to Book Tour, 1 folders (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), General, Smoller/Holzer, 2001; 4 folders (Box 54, Folder 1-4)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), General, The Tour, 2003-2005; 6 folders (Box 54, Folder 5-10)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), General, Tour Positions, 2 folders (Box 54, Folder 11-12)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Notes, 2004; 1 folders (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, 60th Birthday, 1997; 1 folders (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, 100-Day Report Card, 2001; 1 folders (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, 1968-2004; 2 folders (Box 55, Folder 3-4)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, 1970; 1 folders (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, 1971; 1 folders (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, 1972, 1972-2002; 3 folders (Box 55, Folder 7-9)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, 1972 Xmas Bombing, 1975-2005; 1 folders (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, 1973; 1 folders (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, 1974; 2 folders (Box 55, Folder 12-13)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, 1978; 1 folders (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, 2004 Election, 4 folders (Box 55, Folder 15-18)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, 2004 GCAPP Gala and Premiere, 2003-2004; 1 folders (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, 2005 GCAPP Gala and Premiere, 2 folders (Box 56, Folder 1-2)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Afghanistan, 2003; 1 folders (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Agent Orange, 2001-2004; 2 folders (Box 56, Folder 4-5)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Air War, 2000-2005; 2 folders (Box 56, Folder 6-7)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Anti-communism, 1992-1999; 1 folders (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Barbara Walters, 1988-2004; 1 folders (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Beverly Morse, 2000-2005; 5 folders (Box 56, Folder 10-14)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Black Panthers, 1969-2002; 1 folders (Box 56, Folder 15, Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Book Notes from Friends, 2001-2004; 4 folders (Box 56, Folder 16-19)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Book Research, 1994-2001; 3 folders (Box 57, Folder 1-3)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Cambodia, 1997; 1 folders (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Campaign for Economic Democracy (CED), 1976-2003; 3 folders (Box 57, Folder 5-7)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Career, 2000-2005; 1 folders (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, China Syndrome, 1979; 1 folders (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Choice Defense Projects, 2001; 1 folders (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, COINTELPRO, 1973-2002; 1 folders (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Collapse of Military, 1969-2002; 1 folders (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, "Coming Home,", 2002; 2 folders (Box 57, Folder 13-14)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Completion of Prague Tapes, 1990; 2 folders (Box 57, Folder 15-16)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Controversy re: Hanoi, 1973-2004; 1 folders (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Czechoslovakia, 1990; 1 folders (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Documentary, 1972-1986; 3 folders (Box 58, Folder 1-3)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, East Germany, 1988-1990; 2 folders (Box 58, Folder 4-5)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Eastern Europe, 2000-2005; 1 folders (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Eastern Europe General, 1988-1990; 5 folders (Box 58, Folder 7-11)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Eastern Europe Prague Tapes, 1990; 5 folders (Box 58, Folder 12-16)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, End of War, 1979-2003; 2 folders (Box 59, Folder 1-2)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Events of May '69, 1968; 1 folders (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Film: "Coming home,", 1985-2004; 1 folders (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Speeches: Jane Fonda Accepts the Ramona Ripston Award, 2017 Nov. 17; 1 folders (Box 96, Folder 18)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Focal Point, 1972-2003; 4 folders (Box 59, Folder 5-8)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Frankie Jones, 2002-2004; 1 folders (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, F.T.A., 1971-2005; 2 folders (Box 59, Folder 10-11)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Fundraising/Hubbard, 2001; 1 folders (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Hanoi, 1972-2004; 4 folders (Box 59, Folder 13-16)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Henry Jaglom, 1971-2003; 2 folders (Box 59, Folder 17-18)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Ida Nudel, 1984-1985; 2 folders (Box 59, Folder 19-20)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, India, 2000-2005; 1 folders (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Indians, 1990-1997; 4 folders (Box 60, Folder 2-5)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Indochina Peace Campaign (IPC), 1972-2001; 3 folders (Box 60, Folder 6-8)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Intro. To the Enemy/Doll's House, 1974-2003; 2 folders (Box 60, Folder 9-10)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Iraq, 2004; 4 folders (Box 60, Folder 11-14)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Iraq War, 1974-2004; 2 folders (Box 60, Folder 15-16)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Jane, 1971-2004; 4 folders (Box 60, Folder 17-20)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Joe Bangert, 2002; 1 folders (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Jane and Vietnam, 1988-2005; 2 folders (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, John Dean, 2004; 3 folders (Box 61, Folder 4-6)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Joint Emergency Campaign, 2001-2003; 1 folders (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, "Julia" + "China Syndrome", 1979; 1 folders (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Kate Rewrites, 2004; 1 folders (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Kerry, 2004; 3 folders (Box 61, Folder 10-12)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Kissinger, 2001-2002; 1 folders (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Legal Committee, 1996-1998; 3 folders (Box 61, Folder 14-16)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Leni, 2000-2005; 1 folders (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Life Magazine, 23 Apr 1971; 1 folders (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Love Canal, 1979; 1 folders (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Mary Hershberger, 2003; 4 folders (Box 61, Folder 19-22, Box 62, Folder 1-3)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Middle East, 1994; 1 folders (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Misc. Writing Notes, 2003; 1 folders (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, MLK, 2001; 1 folders (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, National Archives, 2004; 2 folders (Box 62, Folder 7-8)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, News Clips Vietnam - Jane 1969-1974, 1970-1987; 2 folders (Box 62, Folder 9-10)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Office Workers, 2003; 1 folders (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Old Gringo, 1989; 1 folders (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Omega Institute, 2003-2004; 1 folders (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, The Other Side, 2000-2005; 2 folders (Box 62, Folder 14-15)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Pentagon Papers, 1972-1999; 3 folders (Box 62, Folder 16-18)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Personal Interviews, 1989-1992; 1 folders (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Piegan Institute, 1993-1998; 1 folders (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Political Campaigns, 2000; 1 folders (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, POWs, 1972-2004; 7 folders (Box 63, Folder 1-7)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Pro Choice Vote, 2001; 1 folders (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Pro-Choice Vote Project, 2000-2001; 4 folders (Box 63, Folder 9-12)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, PSAY Network, 1992-1997; 2 folders (Box 63, Folder 13-14)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Radio Hanoi Broadcast, 1972; 1 folders (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Register, Rally, Run (RRR), 2003; 3 folders (Box 63, Folder 16-18)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Religious Study, 1989-2005; 5 folders (Box 64, Folder 1-5)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Right Wing, 2000-2003; 3 folders (Box 64, Folder 6-8)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Schutts, Jeff Richard, We Say No to Your War!, 1994; 2 folders (Box 64, Folder 9-10)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Stanley & Iris, 1987-1989; 1 folders (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Sue Sally, 2003; 1 folders (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Suit Against Nixon, 1972-1975; 1 folders (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, TED, 1990-2004; 4 folders (Box 64, Folder 14-17)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Tom Era, 1970-2000; 3 folders (Box 65, Folder 1-3)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Tour Staff, 1 folders (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Unknown, 1970-1974; 1 folders (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Vet's Comments, 1963-2003; 1 folders (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Viet Revisionism, 2001-2002; 1 folders (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Vietnam, 1993-2000; 3 folders (Box 65, Folder 8-10)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Vietnam History, 1954-1971; 1 folders (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Vietnam Research, 1954-2004; 3 folders (Box 65, Folder 12-14)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Vietnam Veterans Against the War (VVAW), 1970-2001; 3 folders (Box 65, Folder 15-17, Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, War Crimes, 2004; 3 folders (Box 65, Folder 18-20)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Watergate, 2002-2003; 3 folders (Box 66, Folder 1-3)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Website Controversy, 1999-2002; 1 folders (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, What Is to Be Done, 1990; 1 folders (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, What Is to Be Learned?, 2003; 4 folders (Box 66, Folder 6-9)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Where's Vietnam Notes, 1966-2002; 5 folders (Box 66, Folder 10-14)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Where Is Vietnam?, 2000-2005; 2 folders (Box 66, Folder 15-16, Box 67, Folder 1-2)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Winter Soldier Investigation (WSI), 2004; 1 folders (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Women in the Military, 2002; 1 folders (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Women's History, 1987-2003; 1 folders (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Published: My Life So Far (2005), Research, Workout, 1982-1989; 4 folders (Box 67, Folder 6-9)
  - Published: "On Preventing Early Teen Pregnancy," in Awareness 2008 ed., Kenneth Cole (New York: Melcher Media, 2008), 1 folders (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Published: Prime Time (2011), Correspondence, 2010; 1 folders (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Published: Prime Time (2011), Correspondence, 2014; 1 folders (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Published: Prime Time (2011), Drafts, Drafts, 2004-2009; 1 folders (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Published: Prime Time (2011), Drafts, Reclaiming Our Mojo, 2004-2009; 1 folders (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Published: Prime Time (2011), Outline, 2004-2009; 1 folders (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Published: Prime Time (2011), Research, Age Boom, 2007-2008; 1 folders (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Published: Prime Time (2011), Research, Age Boom Interviews, 2007; 3 folders (Box 68, Folder 2-4)
  - Published: Prime Time (2011), Research, Centenarians, 2004-2009; 1 folders (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Published: Prime Time (2011), Research, Center for Healthy Aging, 2007-2008; 3 folders (Box 68, Folder 6-8)
  - Published: Prime Time (2011), Research, Center for Wise and Healthy Aging, 2004-2009; 3 folders (Box 68, Folder 9-11)
  - Published: Prime Time (2011), Research, Exercise, 2007-2009; 4 folders (Box 68, Folder 12-15)
  - Published: Prime Time (2011), Research, Experts to Interview, 2007; 2 folders (Box 69, Folder 1-2)
  - Published: Prime Time (2011), Research, Interviews, Abramson, Dr. Phyllis, 2004-2009; 1 folders (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Published: Prime Time (2011), Research, Interviews, Achenbaum, Ph.D., W. Andrew, 2004-2009; 1 folders (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Published: Prime Time (2011), Research, Interviews, Bickford, Nathaniel, 2004-2009; 1 folders (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Published: Prime Time (2011), Research, Interviews, Cole, Dr. Johnnetta, 2007; 1 folders (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Published: Prime Time (2011), Research, Interviews, El Saadawi, Dr. Nawal, 2004-2009; 1 folders (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Published: Prime Time (2011), Research, Interviews, Meiyer, Dr. Diane, 2004-2009; 1 folders (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Published: Prime Time (2011), Research, Interviews, Parks, Ph.D., Denise, 2004-2009; 1 folders (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Published: Prime Time (2011), Research, Interviews, Perlmutter, Dr. Marion, 2004-2009; 1 folders (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Published: Prime Time (2011), Research, Interviews, Sprott, Dr. Richard, 2004-2009; 1 folders (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Published: Prime Time (2011), Research, Interviews, Suzman, Dr. Richard, 2004-2009; 1 folders (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Published: Prime Time (2011), Research, Interviews, Weiner, Jonathan, 2004-2009; 1 folders (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Published: Prime Time (2011), Research, JF Center, 2009-2010; 1 folders (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Published: Prime Time (2011), Research, Lump of Labor, 2007-2008; 3 folders (Box 69, Folder 15-17)
  - Published: Prime Time (2011), Research, Mary Catherine Bateson, 2004-2009; 3 folders (Box 70, Folder 1-3)
  - Published: Prime Time (2011), Research, People Interviewed, 2007-2008; 5 folders (Box 70, Folder 4-8)
  - Published: Prime Time (2011), Research, Palliative Care, 2006-2007; 1 folders (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Published: Prime Time (2011), Research, Sex, 1959-2008; 7 folders (Box 70, Folder 10-16)
  - Published: Prime Time (2011), Research, Sexuality, 2007-2009; 4 folders (Box 71, Folder 1-4)
  - Published: Prime Time (2011), Research, Stanford Interviews, 2004-2009; 2 folders (Box 71, Folder 5-6)
  - Published: What Women Want: Help Save Nigerian Girls from Rape and AIDS, 2002; 1 folders (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Unpublished: Notes, 1970-2000; 1 folders (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, [1st] GCAPP Conference, 1996; 1 folders (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, [2nd] GCAPP Conference, 1997; 1 folders (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, [3rd] GCAPP Conference Speech, 1998; 1 folders (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, [4th GCAPP Convention] [Untitled], 1998-1999; 1 folders (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, G-CAPP '99 [4th] Convention Overview, 1998; 1 folders (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, [7th] GCAPP Convention…Dinner Speech, 2002; 1 folders (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, …A Little Bit About Girls, 1995-2005; 1 folders (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, A Tribute Honoring Gregory Peck, 2003; 1 folders (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Unpublished: Speeches, Additions to Press Club Speech, 1998; 1 folders (Box 71, Folder 17)